https://www.ridershack.com/privacy-policy/

Surf's up!
Menu
Surfboards
ShortboardsFish BoardsFunboardsLongboardsSoft BoardsUsed BoardsSale SurfboardsCatch SurfBeaterOdyseaWomperChannel IslandsMid-LengthFishbeardNeckbeard 2Rocket WideOG FlyerWater HogFirewireEl TomoGlazerTwice BakedSeaside and BeyondSeasideDominator 2.0Hayden ShapesHoly GrailHypto KryptoUntitledLostSwordfishRocket ReduxSmooth OperatorCrowd KillerCobra KillerPuddle Jumper HPRNF RetroHydraPyzelGhostPhantomGremlinAstropopPyzAlien 2Surf IndustriesModern7SCreative ArmyGnarlarooSurftechChannel IslandsTakyamaSharp EyeStewartNSP & Surftech BrandDMSTorqChannel IslandsMini LongMod FishMod FunLongboardTec
Gear
FinsSingle FinsTwin FinsThruster FinsQuad FinsTri/Quad FinsSides,Rears & KnubsCaptain Fin CoLeashesComp LeashesStandard LeashesLongboard LeashesTraction1 Piece PadsMulti Piece PadsPads with ArchPads with No ArchFront Foot PadsBoard BagsFishLongboardShortboardTravelBoardsocksSurfboard RacksBikeCarWallWax & AccessoriesSurfboard WaxEar & Nose PlugsRinse & Change GearWetsuit CareFin HardwareKey StorageDing Repair SuppliesBooksEpoxy KitsFiberglass KitsQuick FixResin, Cloth & FillerBackpacks & LuggageGuide BooksSwim FinsBodyboards
Wetsuits
Rip Curl WetsuitsFlashbombE-BombG-BombAggroliteDawn PatrolO'Neill WetsuitsPsycho FreakPsycho 1HyperfreakEpicMens3/2 Fullsuits4/3 FullsuitsSpring Suits & JacketsWomens3/2 Fullsuits4/3 FullsuitsSpring Suits & JacketsKidsBoys 3/2 FullsuitsBoys 4/3 FullsuitsGirls 3/2 FullsuitsGirls 4/3 FullsuitsSpring SuitsRashguardsMensWomensKidsLongsleeveShortsleeveShortsBooties + Hoods + GlovesMens BootiesWomens BootiesGlovesHoodsAccessories + CareChange MatsChange TowelsRinse JugsSurf HatsCleaning & StorageRepairAnti Chaffing Gel
Clothing
MensTopsBottomsBoardshortsFlip FlopsAccessoriesWomensTopsBottomsDressesSwim WearFlip FlopsAccessories
Beach Supply
SunscreenFacesticksLotionsTanningLip BalmRecoveryTowelsStandardOversizeChange RobesHatsBeachSurfTruckerSnap BackFittedSnapbackSunglassesPolarizedFlip FlopsMensWomensKidsWater BottlesCandles & Scents
Watches & Sunglasses
SunglassesWatches
Skateboards
CompletesAccessories
Giftcards
Brands
0
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Go
l
RIDER SHACK | Privacy Policy
What information do we collect? We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: -To improve our website; (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)-To improve customer service; (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)-To process transactions;  Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.-To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature-To send periodic emails; The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.How do we protect your information? We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.Do we use cookies? Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain informationWe use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party links Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into 'My Account' and going to the 'My Account' page. If you wish to delete your account, please email us through our 'Contact Us' page and we will delete your account and all related information within 48 hours.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Your Consent By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. RIDER SHACKwww.ridershack.com13211 W Washington BlvdLos Angeles, CA 90066310-821-7873
Local Pick Up
60 Day Return Policy*
FREE SHIPPING Over $75
Family Owned
Home
Surfboards
Shortboards
Fish Boards
